Yes, I am in YouTube.
Thank you very much.
Let's go cheer up today, shall we?
Okay, let's do our regular thing.
Yes, that's right.
Mabodofu's smelly hands.
I ate with my hands.
Probably, you know, because of the spill.
No doubt.
Okay, let's go.
Join forces,
GO!
GO, GO, GO, GO!
What a surprise.
Thank you very much.
It's so cool at night, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
You surprised me.
I've been saying "tropical shop, tropical shop" for a long time.
What's that? Surprisingly, the daytime is the same as usual.
Yes.
The other day, I was just wandering around like a normal person,
I had a burning heat on my back.
Just now.
Oh, yes, that's right.
I knew it. When the sun goes down, it all goes down at once.
Yeah.
As expected.
Autumn is as expected.
Hey.
So, this week, I'm going to work my shift.
I'm going to work hard.I'll try my best.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
What's wrong?
What's wrong? What did you say?
Nice to meet you.
Oh, you got it wrong.
I don't understand.
I think it's just for the experience,
I think they'd like to have a shot with you.
That's right.
Let's do it.
Please do it, Mr. Sensei.
Yes, sir.
Okay, Ms. Kajiwara.
Good luck!
Hurry up.
Yes.
Yes! Thank you very much. I think you all just did it together. That's right. Here they come!
So, as usual, I would like to ask you to do a very brief alibi for the recording for Friday, September 22nd.
Please do so.
Yes, that's right.
We are a coffee shop where we talk, sing songs, and have a lot of fun.
We are a cheerful and enjoyable coffee shop. We are a cheerful and enjoyable cafe, but Gambandhani, for example, has a special move.
For example, Ganbandhani has a special move, or a special technique. It's nice, isn't it? It's nice, isn't it? Thank you very much.
I just remembered just now that this is my special move, isn't it? I just remembered that it's my special move. Oh, yes.
Can I ask you to take my serve? I'll take it. Can I have you serve? I'll take it. Yes, I'll take it. Yes, of course.
Ichikame-san, may I come in for a moment? Let me come by. May I? Scary, scary, scary.
Rubber-rubber, scary! Pistol!
Ow! Think of it as one of my special moves.
A rubber-rubber pistol. It's not a rip-off at all. There are existing ones, aren't there?
No, that's what they're doing over there, right? Oh, I see. The rubber pistol.
My rubber pistol. Oh, I'm sorry. It's hard to do it every time.
I have to go to white every time. Rubber pistol! Ouch!
I don't mind, but please don't do that. That's not right.
Please get even with him. Rubber band pistol!
Rubber bullets!Gomu Gomu no Mi!
Mi!
I see. Well, well, well, well, well. So, do you have a book of this special move?
No, I don't have a book. Now there are so many fire and rubber pistols.
It was like a gag for a while. A gag?
There was a joke that was very popular among the fans. I don't know why it was so popular.
I don't know why it was so popular. Well, it's a good gag.
I apologize for the short sleeves, but it was actually done in long sleeves. Oh, is that setting also important?
Yes, please leave the three turtles as they are.
Oh, my God! Whoa! Whoa!
Wait, wait, wait, wait. It's in, it's in, it's in. It's in, it's in, it's in.
I can't see you from here. No, no, no. I'm in, I'm in.
Yes, yes. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'll go again.
Okay. Okay, Sangame-san, leave it as it is. I'll go.
Ah! Whoa! Whoa! Aah!
Aah!
This stuff about Nessie is soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo. Sorry, sorry, sorry. What did you say at the end? Nessie.
You said "Nessie. I said Nettie. You say "nettie"?
For some reason, this has become a big hit among his fans. Heh.
Oh, so you are this very Nessie? That's right. Like this.
Oh, I see. It's nice. Did you make it yourself? I made it myself.
Wow, that's great. That's a genuine compliment. What's that again?
Good, good, good. It's good, isn't it? Thank you very much.
I mean, my stuff is like Shonen Jump Weekly, you know? That's right.
It's a cliche. Gabneris.
Well, well, well, well, like that, it's like a special move. Is it a special move, or is it that?
It's like a goi-go-isu, right? Yes, that's right.
Goi goi goi. That's what it means.
It would be nice to have something like that. Yes, it would be.
Well, well, well, it's not like that. So, what is it? I'd like to show the real-time viewers the Sawapon's story.
I'd like to show the "Sawapon" to those who are watching in real time.
Well, it seems to be cold now. The temperature seems to be dropping.
It's really a "Sawapon". I'm already getting a storm of comments.
I've done it, haven't I? I'm sorry.
But Nessie, Nessie is so nice. Really?But Nessie, Nessie is nice. Really?
Nesco's Nessie, right?
It's a one-shot trick that only three people in the world laugh at. That's why I did it.
If there are three people, why not? It was a one-shot trick where only three people laughed.
At first it sounded like a joke. That's right.
I thought "neti" sounded new.
I wondered what "neti" meant. I don't know what neti means.
It was interesting to hear the ones that didn't make sense, and the ones that didn't make sense at all.
It is difficult, isn't it? That's right.
It's all about the person who does it at the time.
So in that respect, Gandharifire is great.
What is Gandharifire?
You said something about Tecto.
I'm like, "Gandalfire!
How much? How much?
I don't know. I don't know.
I said, "Think of something," and he was like, "That's kind of cool,
I'm a gandalfire.
Well, you probably know what I'm talking about.
So, I'll tell you what,
Let's see, let's go.
Today is the 22nd of September,
Tomorrow is the 23rd of September, which is a national holiday.
Oh!
Isn't that still the same? 923, because it's been changing lately.
Holidays are changing these days. It's the same one.
September 23rd. You all know it well.
It's September 23rd. Tomorrow is a national holiday.
What day? I don't know why you don't know, it's September 23rd.
Well, to be more precise, it's like the time of day and night are almost the same. 100.
100.
What's that? What day is it? Reverse night.
Reverse night is when the night is longer.
What day is it? Mr. Cooney?
Dr. Support, may I?
I didn't come up until now, but I had the help of your comment.I never came across it before either, but I took the help of the comments.
End of the day?
Like that's the first time you've ever said that?
Are you okay? Everyone.
It's spring too. It's been a long day so far.
Until August. But then, it gradually became closer and closer to winter.
The nights are getting longer and the days are getting shorter.
From tomorrow, the nights will start getting longer.
So that's how it is. Yes, that's possible. Yes, there is.
Tomorrow, September 23rd, is the day of the Ocean Star.
An oceanic star. Like the solar system. You are not a solar system. You are more like a solar system.
Like that kind of solar system. Solar system. You have planets, the sun, right? That is a fixed star. Mother.
They revolve around it, don't they? Yes, yes. One of them is an oceanic star. If it's a bedrock, you've probably seen Sailor Moon, haven't you?
Yes.
Why Moon? Why Moon? Look at it.
I haven't seen it.
Oh, you haven't seen it.
This, actually, if you've seen Sailor Moon, you've already seen all of Sailor Moon.
Wow.
The moon comes out too, you know. Well, of course, it's Sailor Moon.
So, that Sailor something something something comes out in English or something.
Yes, yes.
Yes, yes. First of all, let's start with the ones closest to the sun.
Ah, ah.
Okay, then.
What?
I'll start with the one closest to the sun, a comet! Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Venus! Venus!
The Subterranean Star! What?
Earth! Oh, my God!
Earth! Earth! I thought I was gonna get hit!
It's so hot!
Yes, Earth! Yes, Earth!
And Mars! Mars.
Jupiter! Yes.
Saturn! Yes. And Uranus! Yes.Saturn! Yes. And Uranus! Yes, sir.
Uh, Neptune! Yes!
And Pluto used to be a friend of mine, but now we've met.
Pluto is the outermost planet of the Sun, if you study it carefully.
I thought it was orbiting the sun, but I was wrong. It is not.
So, it was like, "That's not the solar system. It's not the solar system, is it?
You're not in the solar system, are you? Like, "No, you're not in the solar system. No?
Now, it's all the way to Neptune. Yes.
By the way, you know the Earth in English, don't you?
I just want to make you think.
I want someone to think about it.
Not by myself.
Think for yourself.
Someone else is going to think.
Why is there such a cushion?
I want to think
EARTH.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Mercury, you know Mercury, you like Sailor Mercury, don't you?
Venus... you know this one... remember her from Sailor Moon?
Sailor Moon... come on... come on... push towards the moon...
Don't make up your mind...
Venus... Venus... That's Sailor...
Venus
And Mars is Sailor...
Mars!
You know Jupiter, because it's famous in a song, Sailor
Jupitia.
Jupitia
And Saturn is Sailor
What's Saturn?
Satan.
Uh, Satan.
And Uranus is Sailor.
You didn't get one? There's one that's not.
There's one that's a bit of a geek's delight... Sailor.Sailor, something that would please the enthusiasts.
Sailor?
Ceos?
Sailor.
Eranus.
Yulanus.
and the marine star is Sailor
Neptune
Jesus
In case you're wondering...
I think back then, when Sailor Moon first started, when the original story was written, the famous fairies were still writing, and...
There's also a Sailor Brute, right?
So this is a famous fairy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, that's how it is.
Anyway, the ocean ship is the most distant planet in the solar system at the moment.
We can see them now with astronomical telescopes and rocket launches.
That's one of the things we can do.
I didn't know how far away it was.
That's why today is the Ocean Star Day.
I heard that a scientist discovered it with a telescope.
Isn't that our solar system? Like, "Isn't that our solar system?
Isn't that our solar system?
Hey! They finally found it.
That's amazing!
By the way, that oceanic star is a huge ice planet.
Because it's so far from the sun
It receives very little heat.
The surface temperature of the oceanic star is
-223 degrees!
-223 degrees?
What!
That sounds awfully cold.
Yes, it's cold.Yes, it's cold.
I'm sure it'll be ready soon.
No, no, no.
You go near the sun, then you get off the back.
And then you go, "Wow!
It's all set.
Yes, that's right.
It's all set up.
-I don't even know what 223 degrees is.
I don't understand it at all.
Well, well, well, well...
Let's have another letter...
Let's hear one more letter.
A quote....
Fujio Akatsuka, the manga artist... and author of "Bakamondo the Genius"...
The author... his stomach started rumbling in 2008... and he looks like this...
Fujio Akatsuka, the genius manga artist.
He's the one who told me...
"Idiots are more heroic than scientists and engineers." Thank you very much.
This is very encouraging. Thank you very much.
It's for your own good.
Thank you very much.
I feel better
Hero
Yay!
That's the first time anyone's ever called me a hero.
Well, that's true.
I don't get that often.
I've never been called a hero either.
Come to think of it...
I've never been called a hero.
Yeah, I guess so.
I've never been told I'm a hero.
Okay, well, I'll just...
I think I'm going to go now.
And...the rest
Oh, uh...
Well, let's close the live broadcast before we go any further.
So, if you have any questions, please feel free to send them to us.
So, yes, well, you know...
As you probably know, September is the month of September!
September! Booth Day! Booth Day!
There is someone who had a booth day...
Raise your hand, please.
Yes!
Congratulations!
You're 16?
Yes, I turned 16.
Finally, but 15 and 16 are very different, aren't they?
No, it's different. It's a sensation.
But the feeling in the middle is that you've suddenly become an adult.
I know, I know.
So, um, what?
So, 20 is now, what, 18 is the coming-of-age ceremony?
Yes, that's right.
But there are still restrictions.
Yes, yes, yes.
When you reach your 20th or 21st birthday, you don't really feel like you've reached the age of 20 or 21.
Well...
I think it was before that.
Yes, yes.
It was a long time, wasn't it?
Yes, there were a lot of things.
Not even close.
Next year you'll be Seventy!
Wow, the nose
Nose
Seventy.
Yay!
The year after next, won't you be an eighteen!
Yes, sir.Yes.
Adulthood. And the year after that?
Nineteen!
And 20!
There's still a long way to go, though.
Devil's Charge.
Thank you very much.
Attendance number 16, 16 years old, which comes only once a year.
That's right!
And the price.
It's true!
In honor of 16.
Sixteen yen?
No, it's not.
It's cute.
You should make it 16 yen sometimes.
I'm so excited.
You too, Kashige.
Thank you very much.
Wow, so many other comments.
So many other comments.
Thank you very much.
Other, but you don't get anything directly from me?
Oh, no, let's just give them a little example.
Hiro Power, too.
Thank you very much.
That's great!
Reach & K.
I knew it. 1,600 yen is good, isn't it?
It's a good price.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Nagaoka.
Mr. Kahiho.
Is there anyone here with 160,000 yen or something?
That's amazing.
That's amazing.That's amazing.
It's a red spa.
So, I've prepared a little tampre from the show yet.
What the heck.
I'm so happy.
Well, then...
What is it?
Here you go.
Thank you.
I wonder... Can I open it?
Here you go. It's from Kyoto.
Oh, Kyoto.
That's amazing.
It's true, it's true.
It was 1,616 yen, wasn't it? 1,616 yen.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. It smells so good.
I wonder what it is.
Open.
What's in it?
It smells so good.
It smells really good.
There is a brush attached.
What is this? Cheese?
It smells so good.
I heard that it would be good if you showed it to me.
What is this?
It's quite thick.
I thought it was cheese at first, but it doesn't look like cheese.
It smells really good.
What is it?
Western?
Can I open it?
Nishi Hongwanji.
It smells so good.Smells great.
Oh, wow, that's amazing.
Incense? Incense?
Wow, it smells so good!
Don't eat this!
It's like a Pocky, like a Pritz.
Oh, my God! Thank you so much!
I love this kind of Gamma Nalio.
It smells so good, like incense.
What is that?
What is this? I'm curious.
Does this have anything to do with that? Of course not.
But the miniature size is adorable. It's adorable.
They're so cute!
Oh, there's more! Thank you so much!
Camonai opens these things carefully.
Wow, what's this? - Wow! What's this?
It's a set of these.
I've never seen this before.
You just stick it in the hole.
So this is how you put it up.
What's this? It's where the lungs would fall.
Let's try one of these, shall we?
Oh, it smells so good!
It smells so good!
Oh, yeah!
You mean like this?
Then light the tip.
Light it on fire, like this.
It smells so good!
And then you do it like this.
Very vertical.
Like this.
Smells great!
Smells great!Smells great!
Stylish!
Thank you.
I'm growing up, 16 years old.
I don't think so, but there's some kind of alchemy or something under here.
Fresh.
It's graphic.
No, it's like... It's like a political show or something.
It's like a drama or something.
Thank you!
Congratulations!
It's amazing.
Anyway, the smell.
Yes, it smells great!
It smells so good!
Smells so fresh!
Mr. Crispy, Mr. Moride Don
Mr. Spo
Let's see...
Please wait a minute.
Mr. Sugikatsu
Mr. Dancing Nippori Ebi Buddy
Thank you very much.
Satomi-san
Smells so good!
Momoshiki-san
Yes, it smells so good!
Karate Bill-chan
Thank you, a lot
Thank you very much.
I'm glad
Okay
No, no, no
Thank you very much
One year.One year.
Yes, good.
Well, well, well.
Well, in the meantime, I'm gonna do a little bit of, you know, live distribution.
It'll be over soon.
Yes, sir.
The last one.
I'll start with the last one.
Yes.
We've received a variety of charges.
Yes, sir.
I received a lot of congratulations.
Yes, you did.
Thank you very much.
And last but not least...
At the end.
Yes, ma'am.
Closing greetings.
Ha-ha-ha.
Please do!
Thank you very much for all the congratulations!
Here we go.
Se-no!
Oh, it's going to be a Se-no!
It's going to be a Se-no!
Ah!
Is everyone ready?
Are you ready?
You came out of nowhere.
He's coming.
I'm not sure I'm ready... at all.
I'm ready.
To Ganda.
Fire!
Bye bye!
Next week we start an hour earlier at 7:00 p.m.Next week, we're moving it up an hour to 7:00 p.m.
Yes!
Please come!
Please!
Thank you very much!
Sixteen.
Yes, I'm done.